nearbyfeed.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy - nearbyfeed.com

## Privacy Policy

Nearbyfeed take your privacy seriously. Our Privacy Policy governs the collection and use of any information you provided to Nearbyfeed. Please read the following carefully for our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the platform and services offered by Nearbyfeed, and any information, text, graphics, or other materials uploaded, downloaded or appearing on the Services (collectively referred to as “Service”), you agree that you accept the policies in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any question about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. 

###  Information Collection 

Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with others. Most of the information you provide to us is information you agree to make public. When you create an account to use services provided by Nearbyfeed, you provide some personal information, such as full name, username, password, email, and the like. You may provide Nearbyfeed with additional information, such as a bio, homepage, location, gender, pictures, status and the like. By default, the information provided by you is almost always to be shared with public but you can make the information more private using settings provided by our Service. 

You may choose to indicate your location by check-in at a place or add a venue, and the location information may appear in your status update, and in your profile. If you do so, we may also save exact coordinates to help improve our service. However, please be really careful when labeling or tagging your location or check-in as residence or home, since your location or check-ins may be available to others and/or public, and those information may be published by third parties without our control. If you still want to label or tag a place or check-in as residence or home, we recommend the following ways to protect your privacy: (1) obscure the coordinate of the place by moving the pin on the map before add venue or check-in; (2) do not input any information which can be associated with you (e.g., your real name, user name, phone no, etc) or which is private or confidential in the place name or street or tag. Please note, you can control who can view your location information by editing your privacy setting. In addition, you can delete your check-in history or status posted before anytime from the website, Privacy Setting, or from the mobile applicaitons. You may also request removal of a venue that may contain private information about you (such as your home address) from our Service, by emailing us at privacy@nearbyfeed.com 

Like many other websites, we use cookie technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but cookie is not required to use many part of our Services such as browsing public status update or place. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your browser and may be saved in your computer. Our service may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can edit the options of your browser to turn off the cookies. 

Our Services use a variety of 3rd parties' services to help provide our Services, such as hosting our server, providing map for location, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser when you use our Services, such as cookies or your IP address. 

###  Information Sharing 

Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with others. Information you provice to the Service, such as status, location, bio, name, etc., will be available to users of the Service who you allow to access such information (e.g., followers, and the like). We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party client to use our Services. We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public message or the number of users who interact with your message. 

We may disclose your information to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; or to protect the safety of any person; or to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Nearbyfeed's rights or property. 

If you are a registered user of our Services, you can use the tools provided to your to access or update the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. 

Our Services are not for people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided personal information to our Services without your consent, please contact us immediately. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided personal information to our Services, we will remove such information and terminate the child's account. 

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy

Nearbyfeed may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of this policy will govern our use of your information. By visiting or using the platform, information and services offered by Nearbyfeed after the changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

###  Any Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns about the privacy using the Services, please feel free to contact us at privacy@nearbyfeed.com
